A Finding Aid to the Chuck and Jan Rosenak Research Material, circa 1938-2003, in the Archives of American Art AAA.rosechuc
Archives of American Art
- Photographic Material, circa 1990s; Series 5; (Boxes 13-18; 4.5 linear ft.)
  - Photographs and Negatives, circa 1990s; 5.2
    - Darmafell, Powell "Glassman", (3 photos; 1 contact sheet and negatives) (Box 16, Folder 25)
    - DePrie, Gerald "Creative" (Box 16, Folder 26)
      (5 photos; 1 contact sheet and negatives: Gerald "Creative" DePrie, Charles Wince, and unidentified)
    - Deschillie, Mamie (Box 16, Folder 27)
      (10 photos; negatives; 1 contact sheet and negatives: Mamie Deschillie and Wilford and Lulu Yazzie; 1 contact sheet and negatives, see Johnson Antonio)
    - Dial, Buck (Box 16, Folder 28)
      (1 photo; 1 contact sheet: Buck Dial, Thornton Dial, and Annie Tolliver)
    - Dial, Thornton, Sr., (2 photos; 1 contact sheet, see Buck Dial) (Box 16, Folder 29)
    - Doman, Eileen, (2 photos; 1 contact sheet and negatives) (Box 16, Folder 30)
    - Dulaney, Burgeses, (3 photos; 1 contact sheet and negatives) (Box 16, Folder 31)
    - Ellis, John Robert, (3 photos; 1 contact sheet and negatives, see Melvin Crocker) (Box 16, Folder 32)
    - Ferdinand, Roy, Jr., (7 photos; 1 contact sheet and negatives; 1 contact sheet and negatives, see A. J. Sainte-James Boudrôt Boudreaux) (Box 16, Folder 33)
    - Finster, Howard (Box 16, Folder 34)
      (6 photos; 1 contact sheet and negatives; 1 4 x 5 color transparency of an unidentified paintings by Finster; one photo of the painting The Dreaded Day of Blood)
    - The Flower Man, (1 contact sheet and negatives) (Box 16, Folder 35)
    - Gerdes, John (Box 16, Folder 36)
      (4 photos; 1 contact sheet and negatives: John Gerdes, O. L. "Geech" Samuels, and Wesley "Toothpick King" Stewart)
    - Gibbs, Ezekiel, (1 photo) (Box 16, Folder 37)
    - Gibson, Evelyn, (3 photos; 1 contact sheet and negatives, see Rudolph Valentino Bostic; 1 contact sheet and negatives see Melvin Crocker) (Box 16, Folder 38)
    - Gibson, Sybil, (1 photo; 1 contact sheet and negatives) (Box 16, Folder 39)
    - Godie, Lee, (2 photos) (Box 16, Folder 40)
    - Goodman, Louise Rose (Box 16, Folder 41)
      (3 photos; 1 contact sheet and negatives: Louise Rose Goodman, Manygoats hogan, and Shanto Road; 1 contact sheet and negatives, see Bill Beaver)
    - Gordon, Baron, (1 photo; see also Billy Ray Hussey and Baron Gordon) (Box 16, Folder 42)
    - Gordon, Ellen, (1 photo) (Box 16, Folder 43)
    - Grant, Sam, (2 photos; 1 contact sheet and negatives) (Box 16, Folder 44)
    - Green, Homer (Box 16, Folder 45)
      (2 photos; 1 contact sheet and negatives: Homer Green and Laura McNellis)
    - Greyeyes, Helen, (6 photos; 1 contact sheet and negatives) (Box 16, Folder 46)
    - Growler, Ray, (2 photos) (Box 16, Folder 47)
    - Growler, Ray and Desmond, (2 photos) (Box 16, Folder 48)
    - Halozan, Bertha A., (5 photos; 1 contact sheet and negatives) (Box 16, Folder 49)
    - Hardin, Joseph (Box 16, Folder 50)
      (3 x 5 color snapshot of Harin not taken by Rosenak; 1 photo of an unidentifired painting by Hardin)
    - Hathale Family (Box 16)
      - Hathale, Bruce (Box 16, Folder 51)
        (4 photos; 1 contact sheet and negatives: Bruce Hathale and Hathale hogan; 2 contact sheets and negatives: Bruce Hathale and Fannie and Julia Pete)
      - Hathale, Dinah, Gloria and Christine, (1 photo) (Box 16, Folder 52)
      - Hathale, Dennis (Box 16, Folder 53)
        (2 photos; 1 contact sheet and negatives: Dennis Hathale, Roger Hathale and Sweetwater sign)
      - Hathale, Dennis and Linda, (6 photos; 1 contact sheet and negatives, see Jack Beasley) (Box 16, Folder 54)
      - Hathale, George (Bruce Hathale's son) and Hathale's hogan, (1 photo) (Box 16, Folder 55)
      - Hathale, Roger, (3 photos; 1 contact sheet and negatives, see Dennis Hathale) (Box 16, Folder 56)
      - Hathale, Roger and Dinah, (3 photos; 1 contact sheet and negatives, see Roger Hathale and Roger and Dinah Hathale) (Box 16, Folder 57)
      - Hathale hogan (Box 16, Folder 58)
        (1 photo; 1 contact sheet and negatives: Hathale hogan and Fannie and Julia Pete; 1 contact sheet and negatives, see Bruce Hathale)
      - View from Hathale hogan, (1 photo) (Box 16, Folder 59)
      - Hathale "Church Circle", (1 photo) (Box 16, Folder 60)
    - Hawkes, Gerald, (4 photos; 1 contact sheet and negatives) (Box 16, Folder 61)
    - Harris, Alyne, (4 photos; 1 contact sheet and negatives) (Box 16, Folder 62)
    - Harvey, Bessie, (9 photos; 1 contact sheet and negatives) (Box 16, Folder 63)
    - Herbert Woody (Box 16, Folder 64)
      (2 photos, views from home)
    - Herrera, Nicholas (Box 16, Folder 65)
      (14 photos; 3 contact sheets and negatives; 3 photographs of works of art: El Padre Hijo El Espirito Santo, 1992; El Rito; and San Ysidro)
    - Holder, Frank, (1 photograph; 1 contact sheet and negatives, see Georgia Blizzard) (Box 16, Folder 66)
    - Holmes, Juliet, (2 photos; 1 contact sheet and negatives, see Duke Cahill) (Box 16, Folder 67)
    - Hope, Alvah, (4 photos; 1 contact sheet and negatives) (Box 16, Folder 68)
    - Hot, Dan, (2 photos) (Box 16, Folder 69)
    - Hot, Dan, son, (1 photo) (Box 16, Folder 70)
    - Howell, Robert, (3 photos; 1 contact sheet and negatives, see John Anderson) (Box 16, Folder 71)
    - Hrovat, Joe, (1 contact sheet and negatives) (Box 16, Folder 72)
    - Hudson, Sylvanus, (2 photos; 1 contact sheet and negatives, see Rudolph Valentino Bostic) (Box 16, Folder 73)
    - Hunter, Reverend John "J. L.", (3 photos; 1 contact sheet and negatives: Reverend John J. L. Hunter and Deacon Eddie Moore) (Box 16, Folder 74)
    - Hussey, Billy Ray, (7 photos; 1 contact sheet and negatives, see Georgia Blizzard) (Box 16, Folder 75)
    - Hussey, Billy Ray and Baron Gordon, (1 photo) (Box 16, Folder 76)
    - Hussey, Billy Ray and Michael Croker, (1 photo; 1 contact sheet and negatives) (Box 16, Folder 77)
    - Hussey, Billy Ray, Michael Croker and Lee Kogan, (1 contact sheet and negatives) (Box 16, Folder 78)
    - Hussey, Billy Ray (Box 16, Folder 79)
      (2 photos; 1 contact sheet and negatives of Billy Ray Hussey and kiln)
    - Ignacio, Elizabeth Willeto (Box 16, Folder 80)
      (6 photos; 1 contact sheet and negatives: Elizabeth Willeto Ignacio and census form; 1 contact sheet and negatives, see Delbert, Emma and Wilbert Buck)
    - Ignacio, Elizabeth Willeto and Harold Willeto (Box 16, Folder 81)
      (2 photos; 1 contact sheet and negatives: Elizabeth Willeto Ignacio and Harold Willeto)
    - Isik, Levent (Box 16, Folder 82)
      (2 photos; 1 contact sheet and negatives, see Russell "Smokey" Brown)
    - Jacquaz, Lawrence and Nageezi Trading Post, (4 photos; 1 contact sheet and negatives; 9 3 x 5 snapshots and negatives) (Box 16, Folder 83)
    - Jennings, James Harold (Box 16, Folder 84)
      (1 contact sheet and negatives, see Raymond Coins; 1 contact sheet and negatives: James Harold Jennings and Hubert Walters)
    - John, Edith Herbert (Box 16, Folder 85)
      (3 photos; 1 contact sheet and negatives: Edith Herbert John and Betty Manygoats)
    - John, Edith Herbert and Guy, (4 photos; 1 contact sheet and negatives, see Sheila Antonio) (Box 16, Folder 86)
    - John, Edith Herbert view of home, (1 photo) (Box 16, Folder 87)
    - Johnson, Anderson, (8 photos; 2 contact sheets and negatives) (Box 16, Folder 88)
    - Jones, Clyde (Box 16, Folder 89)
      (4 photos; 1 contact sheet and negatives, see Harold Crowell; 1 contact sheet and negatives: Clyde Jones, Vollis Simpson and Quinton "Q. J." Stephenson)
    - Jones, Frank Albert (Box 16, Folder 90)
      (1 photo, credit Frank Jones Estate)
    - Jones, M. C. ("Five Cent") (Box 16, Folder 91)
      (3 photos; 1 contact sheet and negatives; home of Five Cent Jones 1 photo)
    - Kane, Andy, (1 contact sheet and negatives, see Prophet William J. Blackmon) (Box 16, Folder 92)
    - Kass, Jacob, (2 photos; 1 contact sheet and negatives) (Box 16, Folder 93)
    - Kaye, Myra Tso, (4 photos; 1 contact sheet and negatives) (Box 16, Folder 94)
    - Kennedy, Leon, (9 photos; 2 contact sheets and negatives) (Box 16, Folder 95)
    - Kinney, Charley, (2 photos, 5 x 7) (Box 16, Folder 96)
    - Kinney, Hazel, (3 photos; 1 contact sheet and negatives, see Georgia Blizzard) (Box 16, Folder 97)
    - Kogan, Lee, (1 photo; 1 contact sheet and negative, see Billy Ray Hussey, Michael Croker and Lee Kogan) (Box 16, Folder 98)
    - Lebus, Van, (1 contact sheet and negatives) (Box 16, Folder 99)
    - Lewis, Tim, (2 photos; 1 contact sheet and negatives, see Georgia Blizzard) (Box 16, Folder 100)
    - Light, Joe (Box 16, Folder 101)
      (6 photos; 1 contact sheet and negatives; 1 contact sheet and negatives Minnie and Garland Adkins)
    - Lowe, Warren, (1 contact sheet, see J. P. Scott) (Box 16, Folder 102)
    - Lowe, Warren and Sylvia (Box 16, Folder 103)
      (1 contact sheet and negatives, some group shots, Warren and Sylvia Lowe, Reginald "Reggie" Mitchell and others; negatives, possibly an exhibition in Louisiana of Warren and Sylvia Lowe's collection)
    - Lucas, Charlie (Box 16, Folder 104)
      (4 photos; 1 contact sheet and negatives: Charlie Lucas, Mary T. Smith and Jimmie Lee Sudduth)
    - Ludwiczak, Theodore ("Ted"), (7 photos; 2 contact sheets and negatives) (Box 16, Folder 105)
    - McHorse, Chris (Box 16, Folder 106)
      (2 photos; 1 contact sheet and negatives: Chris McHorse and Faye Tso)
    - Mackay, Rema (Box 16, Folder 107)
      (2 photos; Mackay Body Shop 1 photo; 1 contact sheet and negatives: McKay and Xmeah and Cherry ShaEla'ReEl)
    - McKeeson, Malcomb, (1 contact sheet and negatives) (Box 16, Folder 108)
    - Mackintosh, Dwight (Box 16, Folder 109)
      (5 photos; 1 contact sheet and negatives Dwight Mackintosh and unidentified artists; 1 contact sheet and negatives: Dwight Mackintosh and Jonathan Parker)
    - McMillan, Sam, (3 photos; 1 contact sheet and negatives, see Georgia Blizzard) (Box 16, Folder 110)
    - McNellis, Laura Craig, (2 photos; 1 contact sheet and negatives, see Homer Green) (Box 16, Folder 111)
    - Malone, Ronald (Box 16, Folder 112)
      (7 photos; Malone working 6 photos; Ronald Malone and family 2 photos; view from Malone house 1 photo; 2 contact sheet and negatives; 1 contact sheet and negatives: Ron Malone, Andrew Tsihnahjinnie award, and Rough Rock)
    - Manygoats Family (Box 16)
      - Manygoats, Betty (Box 16, Folder 113)
        (4 photos; 1 contact sheet and negatives, see Edith Herbert John; 1 contact sheet and negatives: Manygoats and Shanto Trading Post)
      - Manygoats, Betty and children Adriana and Anna, (1 photo) (Box 16, Folder 114)
      - Manygoats, Hogan, (2 photos; 1 contact sheet and negatives, see Louise Rose Goodman) (Box 16, Folder 115)
    - Mason, John R., (4 photos; 1 contact sheet and negatives, see Patsy Billups) (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - Mason, John R. Mason and sister Mary Smith, (1 photograph) (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - Mayora, Sergio (Box 17, Folder 3)
      (5 photos; 1 contact sheet and negatives; Jan Rosenak and patron at Weeds bar 1 photo)
    - Merrill, Mary Francis, (2 photos; 1 contact sheet and negatives, see Ralph Bell) (Box 17, Folder 4)
    - Milestone, Mark Casey (Box 17, Folder 5)
      (5 photos; 1 contact sheet and negatives, see Raymond Coins; 1 contact sheet and negatives: Mark Casey Milestone and Smith car)
    - Miller, Reuben "R. A.", (3 photos; 1 contact sheet and negatives, see Zebedee Z. B. Armstrong) (Box 17, Folder 6)
    - Mitchell, Jesse (Box 17, Folder 7)
      (2 photos; 1 contact sheet and negatives: Jesse Mitchell and Willie White)
    - Mitchell, Reginald "Reggie", (4 photos; 1 contact sheet and negatives, see Warren and Sylvia Lowe) (Box 17, Folder 8)
    - Morgan, Ike, (4 photos) (Box 17, Folder 9)
    - Morgan, Sister Gertrude, (1 photo, photographer unknown) (Box 17, Folder 10)
    - Moore, Deacon Eddie (Box 17, Folder 11)
      (1 photo; 1 contact sheet and negatives, see Reverend John "J. L." Hunter; 1 contact sheet and negatives: Deacon Eddie Moore and Isaac Smith)
    - Mulligan, Mark Anthony (Box 17, Folder 12)
      (2 photos; 1 contact sheet and negatives: Mark Anthony Mulligan and Carl Bruno Piwinski)
    - Navajo Scenes (Box 17)
      - Carson Trading Post, (2 photos; 1 contact sheet and negatives, see Fannie and Julia Pete) (Box 17, Folder 13)
      - Chaco Culture National Historic Park (Box 17, Folder 14)
        (1 contact sheet and negatives: Chaco and Lynbrook Trading Post)
      - Keams Canyon Trading Post, (1 photo; 1 contact sheet and negatives, see Ida Sahmie) (Box 17, Folder 15)
      - Lynbook Trading Post, (1 contact sheet and negatives, see Navajo Scenes, Chaco) (Box 17, Folder 16)
      - Nageezi Trading Post, (1 photo; see also Lawrence Jacquaz and Nageezi Trading Post) (Box 17, Folder 17)
      - Old Wagon Road at the gap through Echo Cliffs, (1 photo) (Box 17, Folder 18)
      - Rough Rock Trading Post, (4 photos; 1 contact sheet and negatives; 1 contact sheet and negatives, see Ronald Malone) (Box 17, Folder 19)
      - Sacred Mountain, (2 photos; 1 contact sheet and negatives, see Bill Beaver) (Box 17, Folder 20)
      - Shanto Road, (2 photos; 1 contact sheet and negatives, see Louise Rose Goodman) (Box 17, Folder 21)
      - Shanto Trading Post, (6 photos; 1 contact sheet and negatives, see Manygoats; 1 contact sheet and negatives, see Lulu and Wilford Yazzie) (Box 17, Folder 22)
      - Shiprock, New Mexico, (2 photos; 1 contact sheet and negatives, see Lulu and Wilford Yazzie) (Box 17, Folder 23)
      - Sweetwater, Arizona, (11 photos; 1 contact sheet and negatives, see Lorraine Williams; 1 contact sheet and negatives, see Dennis Hathale; 1 contact sheet and negatives see Robin Willeto) (Box 17, Folder 24)
      - Tsaya Trading Post, (1 photo; 1 contact sheet and negatives, see Bob and Sandy Beyale) (Box 17, Folder 25)
      - Tuba Trading Post, (4 photos) (Box 17, Folder 26)
      - Window Rock, (1 photo; 1 contact sheet and negatives, see Tom Yazzie) (Box 17, Folder 27)
    - Nash, Carl (Box 17, Folder 28)
      (3 photos; 1 contact sheet and negatives: Carl Nash and Reverend L. T. Thomas)
    - Nez, Linda (Box 17, Folder 29)
      (8 photos; Nez home 4 photos; 1 contact sheet and negatives)
    - Parker, Jonathan, (4 photos; 1 contact sheet and negatives, see Dwight Mackintosh) (Box 17, Folder 30)
    - Patterson, Donald, (2 photos; 1 contact sheet and negatives, see Jim Bauer) (Box 17, Folder 31)
    - Pelner, Greg, (2 photos; 1 contact sheet and negatives) (Box 17, Folder 32)
    - Pete, Fannie, (4 photos) (Box 17, Folder 33)
    - Pete, Fannie and Julia (Box 17, Folder 34)
      (2 photos; Pete Hogan 1 photo; 1 contact sheet and negatives: Fannie and Julia Pete and Carson Trading Post; 1 contact sheet and negatives, see Hathale hogan; 1 contact sheet and negatives, see Bruce Hathale)
    - Philpot, David, (3 photos; 1 contact sheet and negatives) (Box 17, Folder 35)
    - Pickle, Frank, (1 photo; 1 contact sheet and negatives, see Archie Byron) (Box 17, Folder 36)
    - Pioche, Dennis, (3 photos; 1 contact sheet and negatives, see Sheila Antonio) (Box 17, Folder 37)
    - Piwinski, Carl Bruno, (1 photo; 1 contact sheet and negatives, see Mark Anthony Mulligan) (Box 17, Folder 38)
    - Polhamus, Melissa, (3 photos; 1 contact sheet and negatives) (Box 17, Folder 39)
    - Ratto, John, (2 photos; 1 contact sheet and negatives, see Duke Cahill) (Box 17, Folder 40)
    - Riggs, Florence (Box 17, Folder 41)
      (4 photos; 3 photos Florence Riggs's hands on loom; 3 photos Florence Riggs and her mother Louise Nez; 1 contact sheet and negatives: Florence Riggs and Linda Nez; 1 contact sheet and negatives: Florence Riggs and Lorraine Williams)
    - Roberg, Robert (Box 17, Folder 42)
      (7 photos; 10 5 x 7 photos; Robert Family with Jan Rosenak 1 11 x 14 photo; 1 contact sheet and negatives)
    - Robertson, Royal (Box 17, Folder 43)
      (1 photo; negatives; 1 contact sheet: Royal Robertson, James "J. P." Scott and David Strickland)
    - Romain, Max (Box 17, Folder 44)
      (2 photos; 1 contact sheet and negatives; 1 color 8 x 10, photo by Jim Linsermon)
    - Rosebrook, Rodney ("Rod") (Box 17, Folder 45)
      (7 photos; 1 contact sheet and negatives; 1 photo of buggy wheel collage, 4 x 5 negative and 8 x 10 photo courtesy of Leslie and Henri Muth; 1 contact sheet and negatives, see Jim Bauer)
    - Sahmie, Ida (Box 17, Folder 46)
      (8 photos; 1 contact sheet; negatives Ida Sahmie, Emmett Tso and Faye Tso; 1 contact sheet negatives: Ida Sahmie and Keams Canyon Trading Post)
    - Samuels, O. L. ("Geech"), (2 photos; 1 contact sheet and negatives, see John Gerdes) (Box 17, Folder 47)
    - Scott, James "J. P." (Box 17, Folder 48)
      (4 photos; negatives; 1 contact sheet: J. P. Scott, Herbert Waide Hemphill, Jr., Jan Rosenak and others at Warren Lowe party, and George Williams; 1 contact sheet, see Royal Robertson)
    - Scott, Lorenzo, (2 photos; 1 contact sheet and negatives, see Archie Byron) (Box 17, Folder 49)
    - Serl, Jon, (2 photos; 1 negative 4 x 5) (Box 17, Folder 50)
    - ShaEla'ReEl, Xmeah, (2 photos; 1 contact sheet and negatives, see McKay) (Box 17, Folder 51)
    - ShaEla'ReEl, Xmeah and Cherry, (4 photos) (Box 17, Folder 52)
    - Sharlhorne, Welmon (Box 17, Folder 53)
      (2 photos by Warren Lowe)
    - Shorman, Ella, (1 photo) (Box 17, Folder 54)
    - Simpson, Vollis (Box 17, Folder 55)
      (1 contact sheet and negatives, see Clyde Jones; 1 contact sheet and negatives: Vollis Simpson, Willie Tarver and Jake McCord)
    - Singleton, Herbert (Box 17, Folder 56)
      (10 photos; 1 photo of work of art; 1 color snapshot of work of art 3 x 5; 1 contact sheet, see Loy A. "Rhinestone Cowboy" Bowlin; negatives, see Loy A. "Rhinestone Cowboy" Bowlin; 1 contact sheet and negatives: Herbert Singleton and Willie White)
    - Smith car, (1 contact sheet and negatives, see Mark Casey Milestone) (Box 17, Folder 57)
    - Smith, Isaac, (4 photos; 1 contact sheet and negatives, see Deacon Eddie Moore) (Box 17, Folder 58)
    - Smith, Mary T., (6 photos; 1 contact sheet and negatives, see Charlie Lucas) (Box 17, Folder 59)
    - Smith, Robert E. (Box 17, Folder 60)
      (3 photos; 1 contact sheet and negatives: Robert E. Smith and dealer Arlene Lewallen)
    - Sparrow car, (1 contact sheet and negatives) (Box 17, Folder 61)
    - Sperger, Hugo, (2 photos) (Box 17, Folder 62)
    - Stephenson, Quinton "Q. J.", (3 photos; 1 contact sheet and negatives, see Clyde Jones) (Box 17, Folder 63)
    - Stewart, Wesley "Toothpick King", (4 photos; 1 contact sheet and negatives, see John Gerdes) (Box 17, Folder 64)
    - Stoss, John, (2 photos; 1 contact sheet and negatives) (Box 17, Folder 65)
    - Strickland, David, (8 photos; negatives; 2 contact sheets and negatives; 1 contact sheet, see Royal Robertson) (Box 17, Folder 66)
    - Sudduth, Jimmy Lee, (8 photos; 1 contact sheet and negatives, see Charlie Lucas) (Box 17, Folder 67)
    - Swearingen, Johnnie, (1 photo 2.5 x 3.25) (Box 17, Folder 68)
    - Talpizon, Ionel, (1 photo; 1 contact sheet and negatives) (Box 17, Folder 69)
    - Taplet, Alfred "Big Al", (3 photos; 1 contact sheet and negatives, see Ivy and Cyril Billiot) (Box 17, Folder 70)
    - Tarver, Willie, (3 photos; 1 contact sheet and negatives, see Vollis Simpson) (Box 17, Folder 71)
    - Tatoo, Tammie, (1 photo; 1 contact sheet and negatives) (Box 17, Folder 72)
    - Thomas, Reverend L. T. "Thunderbolt" (Box 17, Folder 73)
      (4 photos; 1 contact sheet and negatives, see Carl Nash; 1 contact sheet and negatives: Reverend L. T. Thomas and Myrtice West)
    - Todd, Carter, (4 photos; 1 contact sheet and negatives) (Box 17, Folder 74)
    - Tolliver, Annie, (2 photos; 1 contact sheet, see Buck Dial) (Box 17, Folder 75)
    - Tolliver, Mose, (1 photo) (Box 17, Folder 76)
    - Travers, Phillip (Box 17, Folder 77)
      (3 photos; 1 contact sheet and negatives: Phillip Travers and Malcha Zeldis)
    - Tsihnahjinnie, Andrew (Box 17, Folder 78)
      (8 photos; views from Tsihnahjinnie home 2 photos; 1 contact sheet and negatives; 1 contact sheet and negatives, see Ronald Malone)
    - Tso, Emmett, (3 photos; negatives, see Ida Sahmie) (Box 17, Folder 79)
    - Tso, Faye, (7 photos; negatives, see Ida Sahmie; 1 contact sheet and negatives, see Chris McHorse) (Box 17, Folder 80)
    - Vigous, Felix, (4 photos; 1 contact sheet and negatives) (Box 17, Folder 81)
    - Walters, Hubert, (3 photos; 1 contact sheet and negatives, see James Harold Jennings) (Box 17, Folder 82)
    - Warmack, Gregory "Mr. Imagination" (Box 17, Folder 83)
      (8 photos; 1 photo of Chuck Rosenak in Warmack attire; 1 photo of Chuck and Jan Rosenak in Warmack home; 1 contact sheet and negatives)
    - Watson, Willard "Texas Kid", (4 photos; 1 contact sheet and negatives) (Box 17, Folder 84)
    - Wellborn, Annie G., (3 photos; 1 contact sheet and negatives, see Alpha Andrews) (Box 17, Folder 85)
    - West, Myrtice, (4 photos; 1 contact sheet and negatives, see Reverend L. T. Thomas) (Box 17, Folder 86)
    - White, Willie, (3 photos; 1 contact sheet and negatives, see Jesse Mitchell; 1 contact sheet and negatives, see Herbert Singleton) (Box 17, Folder 87)
    - Wilkerson, Knox and Mother, (1 contact sheet and negatives) (Box 17, Folder 88)
    - Willeto Family (Box 17)
      - Willeto, Charlie and family (Box 17, Folder 89)
        (1 5 x 7 photo ca. 1963, photo by R. Willeto; 4 x 5 negatives)
      - Willeto, Harold, (4 photos; see also Elizabeth Willeto Ignacio and Harold Willeto) (Box 17, Folder 90)
      - Willeto, Robin (Box 17, Folder 91)
        (3 photos; 1 contact sheet and negatives: Robin Willeto and Sweetwater)
      - Willeto hogan, (1 photo) (Box 17, Folder 92)
    - Williams, Chuck "Artist Chuckie", (6 photos; 1 contact sheet and negatives; 1 contact sheet and negatives, see A. J. Sainte-James Boudrôt Boudreaux) (Box 17, Folder 93)
    - Williams, George, (2 photos; 1 contact sheet, see J. P. Scott) (Box 17, Folder 94)
    - Williams, Lorraine (Box 17, Folder 95)
      (5 photos; 1 contact sheet and negatives: Lorraine Williams, Lulu Yazzie and children and Navajo Scenes, Sweetwater; 1 contact sheet and negatives, see Florence Riggs)
    - Williams, Rose, (3 photos; 1 contact sheet and negatives, see Silas Claw) (Box 17, Folder 96)
    - Williams, Susie, (1 contact sheet and negatives, see Silas Claw) (Box 17, Folder 97)
    - Willis, Wesley, (6 photos; 1 contact sheet and negatives) (Box 17, Folder 98)
    - Wince, Charles, (2 photos; 1 contact sheet and negatives, see Gerald Creative DePrie) (Box 17, Folder 99)
    - Yazzie, Tom (Box 17, Folder 100)
      (5 photos; Yazzie family negatives; 1 contact sheet and negatives: Tom Yazzie and Window Rock)
    - Yazzie, Lulu, (3 photos; 1 contact sheet and negatives, see Lorraine Williams) (Box 17, Folder 101)
    - Yazzie, Lulu and children, (1 photo; 1 contact sheet and negatives, see Lorraine Williams) (Box 17, Folder 102)
    - Yazzie, Lulu and Wilford (Box 17, Folder 103)
      (6 photos; 1 contact sheet and negatives: Lulu and Wilford Yazzie, Navajo Scenes, Shiprock and Navajo Scenes, Shanto Trading Post; 1 contact sheet and negatives, see Mamie Deschillie)
    - Yazzie, Wilford, (1 photo) (Box 17, Folder 104)
    - Zeldis, Malcha (Box 17, Folder 105)
      (1 photo; 1 contact sheet and negatives: Phillip Travers)
  - Photographs and Negatives for The Saint Makers: Contemporary Santeras y Santeros, circa 1990s; 5.3
    - Alarid, Frank, (1 contact sheet and negatives; 3 photos; 1 contact sheet and negatives, see Cordova) (Box 17, Folder 106)
    - Bimonte, Fernando, (5 photos; contact sheet and negatives, see Jones) (Box 17, Folder 107)
    - Brito, Frank, Sr. (Box 17, Folder 108)